Guide to the Time Inc. Time-Life News Service Records 1935-1987 MS 3009-RG 14
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Staff Files, 1936-1987; 46.8 Linear feet in 49 record cartons
  - Subseries IV.B. Ex-Staff Files, 1943-1987; 16.55 Linear feet in 18 record cartons
    - Holley, Blanche [RESTRICTED], 1978-1984 (Offsite-box R52)
    - Horne, Monica, 1945-1952 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 3)
    - Horne, Monica [RESTRICTED], 1946, 1952 (Offsite-box R52)
    - Howland, Bill, 1945-1947, 1964 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 4)
    - Hoyt, Austin, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 5)
    - Hsieh, S.T., 1956-1965 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 6)
    - Hubbard, Fred, 1953-1964 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 7-12)
    - Hughes, Edward, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 13)
    - Hughes, Edward [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R52)
    - Hughes, Emmet: Correspondence with Luce, 1957-1962 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 14)
    - Hughes, Emmet: Memoranda, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 15)
    - Hughes, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R52)
    - Hunt, George: Project, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 16)
    - Hunte, George, 1949, 1958 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 17)
    - Hurmuses, Paul, 1952-1967 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 18-19)
    - Hutchinson, Paul, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 20)
    - Hutton, Bud, 1952 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 21)
    - Huyck, Phil, 1963 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 22)
    - Iker, Samuel R., 1962-1975 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 23)
    - Iker, Samuel R. [RESTRICTED], 1965-1975 (Offsite-box R52)
    - Ilitch, Fiona, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 24)
    - Ingraham, Reg, 1944 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 25)
    - Iwama, Frank, 1969-1982 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 26)
    - Iwama, Frank [RESTRICTED], 1974-1978 (Offsite-box R52)
    - J: Miscellaneous [EMPTY], undated (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 27)
    - Jackson, C.D., 1957-1965 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 28)
    - Jackson, Edward, 1969-1986 (Offsite-box 3229, Folder 29)
    - Jackson, Edward [RESTRICTED], 1965-1986 (Offsite-box R52)
    - Jacobs, H.P., 1949-1958 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 1)
    - Jacoby, Annalee, 1941-1946 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 2)
    - Janos, Leo H., 1969-1977 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 3-4)
    - Janos, Leo H. [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970, 1977 (Offsite-box R52)
    - Jaroff, Leon, 1959-1964 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 5)
    - Jarvis, Will, 1958-1960 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 6)
    - Jenkins, Ellen Burr [RESTRICTED], 1961-1963 (Offsite-box R52)
    - Jenkisson, John, 1949-1953 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 7)
    - Jennings, Robert C., 1958-1963 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 8)
    - Jermiah, Carolyn, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 9)
    - Jerome, Sarah, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 10)
    - Jessup, Jack, 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 11)
    - Joel, Yale, 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 12)
    - Johnson, Keith, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 13)
    - Johnson, William, 1948, 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 14-15)
    - Johnston, Harry, 1959-1967 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 16)
    - Johnston, Richard, 1946 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 17)
    - Jones, Cranston, 1949-1954 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 18)
    - Jones, Eva G. [RESTRICTED], 1981-1983 (Offsite-box R52)
    - Jones, George, 1949-1951 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 19)
    - Jones, Ivory [RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Jones, Landon Y. [RESTRICTED], 1966 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Jones, Mostyn W. [RESTRICTED], 1976-1977 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Jones, Robert Francis, 1961-1963 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 20)
    - Jones, Robert Francis [RESTRICTED], 1960 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Jones, Vincent E. [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Judson, Horace, 1966-1974 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 21)
    - Judson, Horace [RESTRICTED], 1966-1973 (Offsite-box R53)
    - K: Miscellaneous, 1946-1947, 1955, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 22)
    - K: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kaeser, Evan [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kaiser, Robert B., 1962-1971 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 23-25)
    - Kaiser, Robert B. [RESTRICTED], 1961-1963 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kalb, Barry, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 26-28)
    - Kalb, Barry [RESTRICTED], 1978-1986 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Karnow, Stanley, 1952-1967 (Offsite-box 3230, Folder 29-33)
    - Karnow, Stanley: Research, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 1)
    - Kauffman, Mark, 1946-1961 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 2)
    - Kefauver, Lindsay [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kellett, Susan [RESTRICTED], 1978-1980 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kelly, Frances Popp [RESTRICTED], 1970-1972 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kelly, Marilynda [RESTRICTED], 1970-1972 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kennedy, Raymond, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 3)
    - Kennedy, Raymond [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kennedy, William J., 1958-1960 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 4)
    - Kessel, Dmitri, 1946-1961 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 5)
    - Kin Maung, Ruth, 1953-1957 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 6)
    - Kirp, David Lewis, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 7)
    - Kirp, David Lewis [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kirton, Clarence, 1962 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 8)
    - Kitaoka, Yasuo, 1974 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 9)
    - Klein, Fred, 1944-1964 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 10)
    - Klein, Fred [RESTRICTED], 1960 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Knauth, Percy, 1944-1951, 1959 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 11)
    - Knox, Mimi, 1973-1978 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 12)
    - Knox, Mimi [RESTRICTED], 1974-1979 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Koblick, Karen [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kopkind, Andrew David, 1962-1968 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 13)
    - Kopkind, Andrew David [RESTRICTED], 1961 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kornfeld, Alfred, 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 14)
    - Kraar, Louis, 1962-1972 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 15)
    - Kraar, Louis [RESTRICTED], 1962-1970 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kraft, Diane [RESTRICTED], 1972-1978 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Kraus, Jeanne [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Krehm, William, 1942-1947 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 16)
    - Krementz, Jill, 1970 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 17)
    - Krementz, Jill [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R53)
    - L: Miscellaneous, 1946-1960, 1968 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 18)
    - Laird, Stephen, 1943-1964 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 19)
    - Lake, Beverly, Ann [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Lambert, Bill, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 20)
    - Lambert, Bill [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Lambert, Charles, 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 21)
    - Lambert, Thomas, 1951-1955 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 22)
    - Lamont, Lansing, 1960-1973 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 23-24)
    - Lamont, Lansing [RESTRICTED], 1965-1975 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Lando, Barry M., 1963-1967 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 25-26)
    - Lando, Barry M. [RESTRICTED], 1961-1967 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Langley, Jim, 1961 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 27)
    - Lanius, Charles, 1948, 1957-1969 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 28)
    - Larsen, Jonathan Z., 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 3231, Folder 29)
    - Larsen, Jonathan Z., 1966-1972 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 1)
    - Larsen, Jonathan Z. [RESTRICTED], 1968-1972 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Laurent, Margaret [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Lauterbach, Richard, 1944-1946 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 2)
    - Laybourne, Larry, 1965-1969, 1976 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 3)
    - Lazaro, Noel, 1955-1959 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 4)
    - Lea, Douglas, 1969 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 5)
    - Leavitt, Scot, 1957-1961 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 6-7)
    - Lee, Betty, 1945-1948 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 8)
    - Lee, David, 1969-1978 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 9)
    - Lee, David [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Lee, David Clare, 1969-1977 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 10)
    - Lee, David Clare [RESTRICTED], 1970-1977 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Lee, Gary [RESTRICTED], 1979-1986 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Leen, Nina, 1956-1961 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 11)
    - Lennox, Helen [RESTRICTED], 1969-1973 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Lesh, Carolyn [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Lessing, Erich, 1956-1960 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 12)
    - Levi, Isaac A., 1958-1962 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 13)
    - Levi, Isaac A. [RESTRICTED], 1961-1962 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Levin, Marlin, 1959-1979, 1986 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 14-17)
    - Levin, Marlin [RESTRICTED], 1967-1979 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Levison, 1947-1950 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 18)
    - Levitt, Len, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 19)
    - Levitt, Len [RESTRICTED], 1970-1973 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Lewis, Joe, 1963-1968 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 20)
    - Lewis, Robert L., 1967-1975 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 21-22)
    - Lewis, Robert L. [RESTRICTED], 1970-1975 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Lien, 1969 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 23)
    - Linck, Tony, 1946-1948, 1959 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 24)
    - Lindgren, Helen [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Linen, James, 1957-1962 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 25)
    - Lizer, Eileen Joy [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Louberto, Mary, 1960-1962, 1969-1976 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 26)
    - Louberto, Mary [RESTRICTED], 1969-1976 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Loughran, Tim, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 27)
    - Loughran, Tim [RESTRICTED], 1981-1986 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Lovesy, John, 1960-1967 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 28)
    - Low, Robert, 1946-1949, 1956 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 29)
    - Lower, Elmer, 1947-1950 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 30)
    - Lozano, Rafael, 1956-1968 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 31)
    - Luter, John, 1945-1954 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 32)
    - Lynam, Ruth, 1951-1960 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 33)
    - Lyon, Sandra [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Offsite-box R53)
    - MaCoy, Ramelle, 1952-1956, 1965 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 34)
    - MacBeth, Jack, 1957-1962 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 35)
    - MacGrath, Max, 1959-1961 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 36)
    - Magazine, Minnie [RESTRICTED], 1965-1983 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Magnuson, Ed, 1958-1960 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 37)
    - Mallin, Jay, 1957-1964 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 38)
    - Mallory, Florence [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Mandelkorn, Phil [RESTRICTED], 1967-1969, 1975 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Mangan, Sherry, 1945-1947, 1955 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 39)
    - Manning, Robert, 1958-1964 (Offsite-box 3232, Folder 40)
    - Mannock, Robin, 1966-1970 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 1-2)
    - Mannock, Robin [RESTRICTED], 1966-1967 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Mark, Jeffrey, 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 3)
    - Marmon, William F., 1969-1978 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 4)
    - Marmon, William F. [RESTRICTED], 1968-1978 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Marmon, William F. Jr., 1963-1979 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 5-6)
    - Martin, Dwight, 1952-1960 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 7)
    - Martin, Lois [RESTRICTED], 1969-1985 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Martin, Mary E. [RESTRICTED], 1960-1980 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Martin, Pepper, 1944 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 8)
    - Martin, Tom, 1956-1964 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 9)
    - Mascarenhas, Anthony, 1959-1966 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 10)
    - Matthews, T.S., 1946-1953 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 11)
    - May, George, 1949-1952 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 12)
    - Mcconaughy, James, 1957-1959 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 13-14)
    - McDaniels, Lee [RESTRICTED], 1981-1985 (Offsite-box R53)
    - McElrea, Beatrice [RESTRICTED], 1958-1966 (Offsite-box R53)
    - McHale, Bill, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 15)
    - McHale, Bill [RESTRICTED], 1959 (Offsite-box R53)
    - McHale, Connie, 1963-1972, 1978 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 16)
    - McHale, Connie [RESTRICTED], 1963, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box R53)
    - McHale, William, 1961-1967 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 17)
    - McLucas, Renee G. [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Offsite-box R53)
    - McManus, Michael J., 1962-1968 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 18)
    - McManus, Michael J. [RESTRICTED], 1962-1963 (Offsite-box R53)
    - McNamara, Mary, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 19)
    - Melvoin, Jeff, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 20)
    - Melvoin, Jeff [RESTRICTED], 1978-1984 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Meyerson, Harvey, 1963 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 21)
    - Miki, Jun, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 22)
    - Milewski, Ronald [RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Miller, Harry, 1943-1949 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 23)
    - Mills, Hillis, 1951 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 24)
    - Mitchell, William [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Offsite-box R53)
    - Moeser, Bill [RESTRICTED], 1961-1964 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Moffett, Hugh, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 25)
    - Moor, Paul, 1958-1961 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 26)
    - Moosa, Spencer, 1954 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 27)
    - Moritz, Michael [RESTRICTED], 1978-1984 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Morrall, June D. [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Morris, Bernie [RESTRICTED], 1961-1962 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Morris, Dudley [RESTRICTED], 1961-1964 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Murphy, Arthur, 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 28)
    - Murphy, Kenneth [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Murphy, Charles, 1945-1948, 1959-1961 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 29)
    - Mydan, Misty, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 30)
    - Neff, Donald, 1969-1980 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 31)
    - Neff, Donald [RESTRICTED], 1965-1981 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Neville, Robert, 1949-1957, 1970 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 32)
    - Newton, Donald, 1945-1952 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 33)
    - Novak, Michael, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 34)
    - Nuncio, Lucy [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Offsite-box R54)
    - O'Connor, Barbara, 1948-1951 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 35)
    - Ogle, Ed, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 3233, Folder 36)
    - Ogle, Ed, 1969-1975 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 1)
    - Ogle, Ed [RESTRICTED], 1967-1987 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Olsen, Milton, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 2)
    - O'Neill, Martin, 1950-1951 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 3)
    - On Pe, 1951-1954 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 4)
    - Ortega, Sara, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 5)
    - Osbourne, John, 1950-1957 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 6)
    - O'Sheel, Patrick, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 7)
    - Pain, William, 1956 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 8)
    - Parkin, Patsy, 1959 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 9)
    - Parks, Michael, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 10)
    - Patterson, Jim, 1969-1978 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 11)
    - Patterson, Jim [RESTRICTED], 1969-1978 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Paul, Lynda [RESTRICTED], 1980-1984 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Pauly, Adrienne L., 1965-1969 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 12-13)
    - Pauly, Adrienne L. [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Peckham, Content, 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 14)
    - Pedreguera, Cynthia [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Pena, Pedro, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 15)
    - Pensa, Hannie, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 16)
    - Perry, Oliverio, 1945-1948 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 17)
    - Phillips, John, 1948-1951 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 18)
    - Phillips, Ruby, 1946 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 19)
    - Philpot, Bernadette [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Pidge, Robert, 1949 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 20)
    - Pinkerton, Ruth, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 21)
    - Pollard, Richard, 1961 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 22)
    - Preston, Hart, 1944 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 23)
    - Pribichevich, Stoyan, 1944-1948 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 24)
    - Price, William and Videt, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 25)
    - Price, William and Violet [RESTRICTED], 1947 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Quivreux, Louis, 1946-1951 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 26)
    - Ragsdale, Wilmott, 1944-1946 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 27)
    - Rajagopala, 1949 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 28)
    - Ralls, Diane T. [RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Rambeau, Marcele, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 29)
    - Ramrahka, Priya, 1968 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 30)
    - Randal, Jonathan, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 31-32)
    - Randal, Jonathan [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Rangaswami, Achel, 1951-1962 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 33)
    - Rappleye, Willard, 1957-1963 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 34)
    - Raynolds, Ron, 1951 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 35)
    - Raynolds, Ron [RESTRICTED], 1951 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Reid, Ludivina [RESTRICTED], 1979-1987 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Reingold, Joel, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 36)
    - Richardson, David, 1945-1956 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 37)
    - Riley, John H. [RESTRICTED], 1964-1965 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Rinehart, Jonathan, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 38)
    - Roach, Irene [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Roberts, Gary [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Roberts, John W. (Bill), 1958-1960 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 39)
    - Robertson, Ruth, 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 40)
    - Rohrich, Margaret, 1958-1962 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 41)
    - Ronan, Elizabeth [RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Rose, Jerry, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 42)
    - Rosenhouse, Harvey, 1951-1966 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 43-44)
    - Ross, Norman, 1957-1961 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 45)
    - Rumwell, Miriam, 1962-1968 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 46)
    - Ryan, Edwards Q. [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R54)
    - S: Miscellaneous, 1946-1950, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 47)
    - Saar, John, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 48)
    - Saddler, Jeanne [RESTRICTED], 1976-1983 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Salzberg, Belinda, 1979 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 49)
    - Sammataro, Lisa [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Santos, Gill, 1969 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 50)
    - Saporiti, Piero, 1959-1967 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 51-52)
    - Schardt, Arlie W., 1962-1968 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 53)
    - Scharneck, Michael [RESTRICTED], 1973-1987 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Schindehette, Susan, 1976-1982 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 54)
    - Schindehette, Susan [RESTRICTED], 1976-1981 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Schoch, Jaqueline [RESTRICTED], 1961 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Scholl, Jane, 1959-1961 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 55)
    - Schutzer, Paul, 1961-1967 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 56)
    - Schwinner, Christian, 1970 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 57)
    - Scott, John, 1973-1985 (Offsite-box 3234, Folder 58-59)
    - Scott, John [RESTRICTED], 1974-1984 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Shamberg, Michael A., 1969 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 1)
    - Shea, Frank, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 2)
    - Sheldon, Louise (Bruder), 1961 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 3)
    - Shields, Eileen, 1973-1981 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 4)
    - Shields, Eileen [RESTRICTED], 1975-1981 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Shook, Ed, 1962-1969 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 5)
    - Shook, Ed [RESTRICTED], 1967-1969 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Siegel, Eleanor [RESTRICTED], 1980-1983 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Silva, Michel "Mike", 1957-1960 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 6)
    - Sinclair, Patricia, 1976-1982 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 7)
    - Sinclair, Patricia [RESTRICTED], 1976-1982 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Skolnick, Ruth [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Smith, Homer, 1949-1963 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Robert M., 1965-1968 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Robert T., 1961-1968 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Robert T. [RESTRICTED], 1961 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Snell, David, 1953-1962 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 11)
    - Sochurek, Howard, 1950-1962 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 12-13)
    - Stalev, Gertrude P. [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Stanley, Edith M. [RESTRICTED], 1982-1987 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Stein, Arthur [RESTRICTED], 1962 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Stein, Jane E. [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Stewart, Carol Lyn [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Still, Larry, 1964-1970 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 14)
    - Still, Larry [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Stoiber, Carlton, 1965 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 15)
    - Stoiber, Carlton [RESTRICTED], 1965 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Sully, Francois, 1952-1959 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 16)
    - Suro, Roberto, 1979-1985 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 17-18)
    - Suro, Roberto [RESTRICTED], 1978-1981 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Suydam, Henry, 1959-1961 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 19)
    - Taylor, John M., 1963 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 20)
    - Testa, Diane A. [RESTRICTED], 1983-1986 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Thai, Binh Don [RESTRICTED], 1974-1986 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Thimmesch, Nick, 1959-1967 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 21)
    - Thimmesch, Nick [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Thomas, Evan, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 22)
    - Thomas, Evan [RESTRICTED], 1979-1983 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Thorne, John, 1953-1956 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 23)
    - Thorsen, Karen, 1972 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 24)
    - Tifft, Tom, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 25)
    - Tompkins, John [RESTRICTED], 1970-1981 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Tompkins, Leslie [RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Tower, Courtney, 1965-1969 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 26)
    - Tower, Courtney [RESTRICTED], 1967-1969 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Trillin, Calvin (Bud), 1958-1962 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 27)
    - Troelstrup, Glenn (Skip), 1967-1970 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 28)
    - Troelstrup, Glenn (Skip) [RESTRICTED], 1967-1970 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Trombley, William [RESTRICTED], 1959-1961 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Turner, Terry, 1961 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 29)
    - Underwood, Don, 1960 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 30)
    - Vaidya, Suresh, 1944-1951, 1957 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 31)
    - Valk, Leslie [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Vallenilla, Josephina, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 32)
    - Van Vyve, Guy, 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 33)
    - Van Walsum, Tineke, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 34)
    - Vandivert, William and Rita, 1941-1948 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 35)
    - Vatja, Ferenc, 1956 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 36)
    - Vatja, Ferenec [RESTRICTED], 1956 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Vidar, Frede, 1946-1950 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 37)
    - Vinson, Curtis, 1945 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 38)
    - Voigt, George, 1952-1961 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 39)
    - Von Balluseck, D.J., 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 40)
    - Von Hildebrand, Franz, 1954-1956 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 41)
    - Vondracek, M. Jon, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 42)
    - Vondracek, M. Jon [RESTRICTED], 1964 (Offsite-box R54)
    - W: Miscellaneous, 1954, 1970 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 43)
    - Waldman, Jules, 1946-1949, 1951 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 44)
    - Walker, Hank, 1948-1950, 1957-1962 (Offsite-box 3235, Folder 45-46)
    - Walker, John, 1944-1951, 1960 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 1-2)
    - Wallace, Henry, 1941-1957 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 3)
    - Wallis, Carol, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 4)
    - Wallis, Carol [RESTRICTED], 1960 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Walton, William, 1942-1945 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 5)
    - Wayman, Stanley, 1961-1963 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 6)
    - Waymen, Stanley [RESTRICTED], 1961-1962 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Weber, Carlos, 1949-1955 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 7)
    - Weekes, Richard, 1954-1957 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 8)
    - Weekes, Richard [RESTRICTED], 1954-1956 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Welles, Sam, 1947-1952 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 9)
    - Welsh, Mary, 1944-1946 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 10)
    - Wertenbaker, Charles, 1944-1947, 1955 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 11)
    - Werther, Betty (Azancot), 1962-1967 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 12)
    - Werther, Betty (Azancot) [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R54)
    - Weston, Joe, 1945-1948 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 13)
    - Weston, Mervyn, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 3236, Folder 14)